const Communalism = [
	{
		questionText: 'Who is the author of the book "Communalism in Modern India"?',
		ans: ['Bipin Chandra'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'How many forms of communalism are there according to Ram Ahuja?',
		ans: ['3'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Who classified communalism into six types?',
		ans: ['TK Oommen'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which commission was constituted in 1970 on the Maharashtra communal riots?',
		ans: ['Madan'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'In which year National Integrational Council (NIC) was established?',
		ans: ['1962'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which among the following commission was appointed in 2009 on the Ayodhya incident?',
		ans: ['Liberhan'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which commission was set up in 1970 on the Godhra riots?',
		ans: ['Nanavati-Mehta'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Who is the Chairman of National Foundation for Communal Harmony?',
		ans: ['Prime Minister'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'What is the rank of India in Global Peace Index (GPI) 2023?',
		ans: ['126 out of 163'],
	},
	{
		questionText: ' In which year Rashtriya Swayam Sevak Sangh (RSS) was established?',
		ans: ['1929'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Who formed the organisation Rashtriya Swayam Sevak Sangh (RSS)?',
		ans: ['KB Hegdewar'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Who is the current Sarsanghchalak of the Rashtriya Swayamsevak Sangh (RSS)',
		ans: ['Mohan Bhagwat '],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Who is/are the founder of Vishwa Hindu Parishad (VHP)?',
		ans: ['Swami Chinmayananda', 'Apte', 'Golwalker'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'When did terrorists attack Indian Parliament?',
		ans: ['Dec 11, 2003'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which train is commonly known as Friendship Express and was started between India and Pakistan?',
		ans: ['Samjhauta Express'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Mumbai Attacks ',
		ans: ['26/11/2008'],
	},

];

export default Communalism;
